Here
we go.
I can't
control.
around.
Happy.
Heat. Heat.
Do you remember?
Are you
Don't be well.
Green.
Yeah, we can hear you well.
>> All right, cool. Um,
good to see every everybody. Um, brain's
a little fried right now. Um, first off,
just kind of want to thank the staff,
uh, the scouting staff, the coaches,
football operations, everybody involved
for what we feel is a successful draft.
Uh, we felt like we definitely got
better. We challenged the roster in a
lot of spots. Um, gained a lot of depth
in a lot in a lot of areas. Um, so yeah,
we feel feel good about what we
accomplished during the draft and
excited about things moving forward and
we're obviously headed in the right
direction. So, um, with that, I'll open
it up to any questions.
>> We'll kick things off to Joe Pson.
>> Hey, Dan. Um,
>> what's up, Joe?
>> Good to see you, man. You, too. Sorry,
it's getting getting a little dark over
here. You're good. um once you traded
back to 227. Um what about I heard you
talk about um challenging the roster and
building depth. Did did you draft anyone
this weekend you think will start from
day one?
>> Um you know I think everybody that we
draft that you know I think they'll all
have the opportunity to compete. Um and
that's what we're all about here. Myself
and coach and the rest of the staff. We
want to bring guys in to challenge the
roster and have them compete. And you
know, we bought we bought in a bunch of
competitors during this draft and
they're going to have a chance to
compete and show us what they can do and
uh it'll be fun to watch.
>> Which of these guys do you think has the
best chance to make the biggest earliest
impact?
>> Uh I think it's up to them. You know, I
think I'm uh excited about all the guys
that we drafted. Otherwise, you know, we
wouldn't have drafted them. So, they're
all going to have the opportunity to
come in and compete, and we're excited
to see what they can do.
>> Are you considering bringing in another
uh undrafted quarterback?
>> Uh potentially potentially we'll we'll
do that and have four quarterbacks,
which we really haven't had since I
don't think we've been here, but yeah,
there's definitely the potential for for
that.
>> You think it's likely?
>> Yeah, I do.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
Alex Zitllo.
>> Hey Dan, congrats on um getting through
another NFL draft.
>> Thanks. What's up, Alex?
>> What's up, man? Um uh particularly on
day three, there seemed to be a couple
guys who um uh who fell to you guys. Um
particularly uh Zaki Wheatley and um and
Sam Heck. Are those two guys when you
had the opportunity to draft them, were
were you surprised that they were still
available at um when you got the chance
to take them?
>> Uh yeah, a little bit. You know, I think
uh I think you saw us kind of maneuver
around the board a little bit. Uh just
looking at our board, you know, we had a
handful of players that we had up there.
So, we're like, "Hey, we like these
guys. Like, they're all guys that we
feel like can help us." So, we're like,
"Let's trade back.
gain more picks, gain more value, and
you know, we did that and and it worked
out in our favor at the end.
>> Specifically about Ziki, how do you see
him fitting into the this defense?
>> Yeah, you know, just a big, long,
physical guy. Um, he fits the DNA that
we want, the type of competitor that we
want. Um, he can play the post, he can
play up in the box, he can do a lot of
things for our defense that we're
excited about. Any
more questions?
Cass.
>> Hey Dan, how's it going?
>> What's up, Cassidy?
>> Um, you had a couple of guys today that
made it through college or at least the
last couple years without a single
penalty. Is Is that just kind of a
coincidence or is that something that
y'all value and look at?
>> I mean, obviously we don't want
penalties. Um, I think it's more a
coincidence than than anything. Um,
honestly, I didn't even really know
that. That's kind of cool, though.
>> Yeah, I think it was uh Wheatley and Hec
made it through without a penalty in
college or at least last couple of
years. And then on Will Lee
specifically, he he comes off the tape
like really just kind of tenacious. How
important is that in a safety back
there?
>> Yeah, you know, corner safety. Um,
that's what we want. You know, that's
our identity. you know, we want to be
physical, we want to be tough, we want
to be competitive. And, you know, we
we're drafting those type of guys in our
culture. And, um, you know, I think
every one of those guys that we drafted,
you know, from the first round all the
way down to the seventh, they they
embody that
>> Darren Gant followed by K.
>> Dan, specifically to Heck at center,
what did you guys see in him that you
like and and how do you see him
competing right out of the gate? Yeah,
he's going to have a chance to compete.
Um, I think first and foremost, you see
his initial quickness. Uh, he's really
good with angles. You know, he can reach
guys. He's good with his hands, getting
his hands inside, controlling blockers,
and staying staying sticky on blocks.
Um, I would say is the biggest thing
with him, staying on his feet, keeping
his balance. Um, he's another guy that
can work to the second level. He can get
out in space as a puller. Um, so there's
a lot of things that we like about him.
>> Was it a priority for you this weekend
to make that room not only deeper, but
younger as you look at the makeup of the
offensive line as a whole?
>> Yeah, you know, I I definitely think we
need to add some youth in there, you
know, on the interior and outside of
tackle and feel like we accomplish that
and, you know, we'll do some things and
undraft the free agency as well that'll
again add to the competition and the and
the depth out there.
Hey Dan, thanks for doing this. Um,
without setting myself up to be made fun
of because of how I pronounce the kid's
name uh by Joe. Uh, Jackson, the guy you
just added from Miami of Ohio. Um, do
you see him as kind of a special teams
cog or what what's your outlook on him?
He doesn't have a lot of playing time
prior to last year.
>> Yeah, good player. Uh, really good
instincts. He can run. He plays fast. uh
he sees it really well. Uh a guy that
we're obviously excited about. You know,
I think he's definitely going to be able
to contribute on special teams and again
like like every area like he's going to
have a chance to compete and show us
what he can do.
>> And then with Will Lee, um do you see
him primarily working outside
boundarywise? I know he brought up how
much he likes doing press man, but
obviously that's not something you guys
do a ton. Um, do you guys see him as
like a long-term outside cornerback?
>> Yeah. Um, you know, I think obviously
I'll leave that up to the coaches for
what they want to do with him. Um, at
Texas A&M, he played on the outside and
he's really good at press and and I
think he's a guy that as he continues to
grow and mature in the game, he'll be
able to, you know, figure out off
coverage and some of the things that we
do schematically. I think he's just a
really good fit for us by the way he
plays, the temperament he plays with,
the swag he plays with out there. Uh
just a guy that we really loved.
>> Joe Pson followed by Sheena quick.
>> Um Dan is Dan or Dave can address this
or both of you. Kind of following up on
Darren's question. Were was this a draft
where you you guys wanted to, you know,
kind of look longterm more so maybe than
than short term?
>> Oh, I'll answer that. I mean, I for for
me it's always about right now, uh, this
season and what we're doing and, um,
trying to make sure that we can get the
most out of our guys that we currently
have. We always start with our roster,
but then, you know, try to find guys
that fit the traits and characteristics,
personality of who the Panthers are. Um,
and that's what we were looking for is
just get more of that. And, uh, it's
going to be the same thing every year.
You know, can we, how can we make the
2026 Panthers the best possible unit
that we can make it. And, um, if we have
guys that, you know, bring a certain
skill set at any position, uh, to give
them a chance to compete and be out
there, you know, we just feel like it
elevates the whole group.
And then back to Dan. Um is there's a
lot all every year really since you took
over people uh and you have drafted
tight ends, but there's this feeling I
think that you guys go need to go get a
tight a number one tight end. Is that
shared in in the building or I don't
know. You you addressed it a little bit
last week. Yeah, we have we have a lot
of confidence in the guys that are on
our roster. And I said that before, you
know, with Tommy and with Mitch and with
Javian and James Mitchell and, you know,
we we have some guys that we're excited
about. And, you know, again, we'll
always look for, you know, avenues to
make the roster better. If we feel like
we need to, you know, figure figure out
tight end and bring a different skill
set in, then we'll do that. But right
now, we feel good about it. And then
Dan, any positions where you feel like
you're still maybe a little light,
whether it's inside linebacker, even
corner?
>> Uh, you know, I think again, we're we're
always going to find ways. We're never
going to be content. We're never we're
never just going to sit there. We're
just going to try to add as much depth
and competition to the roster as
possible. And, you know, we'll we'll
keep doing that moving forward.
>> Good afternoon, guys. How are you?
>> Good. How you doing?
>> Um just a question about uh Lee and
Wheatley. What specifically did you guys
see in those two players that made them
a fit for the corner and um safety rooms
that you guys have right now?
>> Lee Lee and Wheatley.
>> Yeah. Will Lee?
>> Oh yeah.
>> Um you want to go?
>> Yeah, I'll take it. Yeah. Um you know,
we look for play style first and
foremost. um trying to project, you
know, the the athletic ability to
contribute is obviously a big part of
it, but then once we kind of know and
identify guys that we feel like can can
impact us and can play in the NFL uh
from an athletic standpoint, then we go
to play style. And you know, Will Lee,
Dan kind of talked about a little bit,
the length, uh the aggressiveness, his
ability to play physical um at the at
the attack point, whether it's on bubble
screens or getting involved in the run
game. we ask our corners to tackle, you
know, and and be a part of the fit um in
our system with our crack or replace
rules and different things like that.
So, uh we felt like he really fit that
mold. And then for Zaki Wheatley, he's
just a really in instinctive player, a
physical player. Uh shows up downhill,
takes really good angles, runs downhill.
um he's all over the field and uh you
know just that kind of activity on the
back half is it's really crucial for how
we play football and and guys being able
to see the formation, anticipate
concepts and then show up physically and
play with that type of attitude that
we're looking for. We had a great time
um you know meeting with uh Zaki at the
combine and just kind of picking his
brain about what he knew, what he was
looking for and um where he came from
and how he's become the player that he's
come and we just loved all the
background and everything and it really
shows on on film and um he was one of my
favorite guys just through the process
to see him and the play style that he
brought.
>> Thanks guys.
>> We have time for just a few more. We'll
go back to Mike K.
Hey Dave. Um, this running back class
was not particularly deep, at least on
the outside looking in and the
selections that were made. You've had
Jonathan in the program for about a
week. Obviously, you're not doing any
contact. You drafted ETN last year. I
know we're talking about the moves you
did make, but the fact that you guys
didn't push for a running back with how
much you publicly talk about wanting to
run the ball. What does that say about
those two guys and your guys's outlook
on them?
>> Well, it goes beyond that, too. you
know, AJ Dylan's here. Um, you know,
Trey Tyus is a guy we're really excited
about getting to see uh coming up here
when we get into camp in the preseason
games and and uh and Montreal is another
guy who, you know, played at a really
high level in college and and is is
finding his way in the pros, but we were
able to bring those guys in. We're
excited to see what they can do. And
when we start with this process, we
always, you know, as we're looking at
players in the draft, we kind of look at
them compared to our roster, compared to
the guys we have. who is this guy
competing with in this room? Like where
do we see them being able to try to
affect it? And we got a bunch of guys
that were really excited about and you
know, of course you talked about um
Jonathan and and Trevor, you know, um in
in that conversation as well and and we
have high hopes for Jonathan, you know,
and and he looks great right now. Um
can't wait to, you know, in the smartest
way possible get him out there and
expose him at the right time and um and
get him accustomed to the things that
we're doing. But um yeah, I love that
group and love what Bernie Palmerly is
doing with them and and how they attack
it and you know, we kind of tell them
you set the tone for the offense and so
we love the way those guys are built.
>> And we haven't been able to talk to you
about it yet, but Trevan and JT, are
they both participating in the program
as well?
>> Yeah. Um that Trevan came back. He's
he's doing really great in terms of
getting back out there. JT has been
cleared. Um is doing more and more. So,
but right now as we know, you know,
they're it's wait room and and meetings
right now. So, until we get onto the
field and kind of move them around, uh
we still got to be smart about all that
stuff.
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you.
>> All right, guys. That's all the
questions we have for you today. Thank
you so much for taking the time.
>> Thanks, guys.
>> All right. Thank you.